horseracegame.com 2011-01-06

# Privacy Policy for Our Racing Games - Horse Racing Simulation, LLC

Home : Privacy Policy

### Privacy Statement for www.horseracegame.com

Horse Racing Simulation, LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We believe that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website: [http://www.horseracegame.com](http://www.horseracegame.com/ "Horse Racing Fantasy").

#### Personal Information Collected

We collect the following personal information when registering for our free game: your first and last name, your email address, a user identification (user ID), year of birth, zip code (if you’re a resident of the United States) and country. We utilize only email addresses to communicate with our members. The amount of communication depends on the level of your engagement with our game and community. Players can opt out or opt in for individual communications specifically associated with certain aspects of our game and community in which players are active. In addition, a player can opt out of all email communications at any time.

Our site links to our online store which uses an order form for customers to order products and services. During the ordering process we collect your name, mailing address, email address and telephone number (Contact Information) and your account or credit card information (Financial Information). Our online store will charge your credit card or account for the products and services you order. We use your name and address to ship your order if you selected the US Mail shipping option. We use your email address to send you download instructions and to inform you of program bug fixes, new product releases and new product offerings such as horse data files. We use your telephone number to contact you in the event of a problem with your order or your installation. You may opt-out of future contract from us; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Occasionally we run online surveys, contests or promotions for additional products and services that we sell. You will be periodically contacted with these opportunities. If you wish to no longer receive these particular mailings from us, you have the option to opt out of general solicitation emails while still receiving general game communications. Of course, at any time, a player can opt out of all communications by simply clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email communication we send.

Finally, unregistered users may request our Demonstration Version via email. In this case we only collect the email address of the requestor. Requestors may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our site contains links to other sites. [www.horseracegame.com](http://www.horseracegame.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Security

Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Any personal information you provide is encrypted prior to transmission. We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card information during our online checkout process. In addition, we utilize the same encryption standard when transferring your credit card data to our internal fulfillment system.

#### Confidentiality and Sharing of Information _(Revised 2/7/2003)_

We will keep your Contact Information and Financial Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site allows our users to opt out of our email list by either clicking on the opt out selection on each and every email we send or by simply sending an email to [support@horseracegame.com](mailto:support@horseracegame.com) with the subject ‘Opt Me Out’. All such requests are honored promptly, usually within 24 to 48 hours.

#### Correct/Update of Information

Our site allows users to Contact us to specify changes to information previously provided.

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can Contact us electronically or write to:

> Privacy Questions  
>  Horse Racing Simulation, LLC  
>  3230 E. Flamingo Road, Ste. 8-307  
>  Las Vegas, NV 89121

#### Glossary of Terms

**SSL Encryption** \- A method by which information transmitted across the Internet is scrambled to the point where it's virtually indecipherable by anyone who should intercept the data before it reaches its destination. Most all reputable online stores make use of SSL encryption to request credit card information and other sensitive data from their customers. Web pages where SSL encryption is activated are typically identified by a lock or key symbol displayed somewhere in your browser. Refer to your browser's documentation for the specific symbol and location.

Home · About Us · Features · Quotes · Screenshots · Add-ons  
[Free Game](http://www.horseracegame.com/dl.php) · Free Stuff · Links · Community · Tournament Play  
Horse Racing Videos · Horse Racetracks · Horse Racing History  
Stakes Races · Thoroughbred Pedigree · Contact Us · Support   
[2010 Kentucky Derby](http://www.horseracingnation.com/probables/2010_Kentucky_Derby_G1/2010_kentucky_derby_horses_contenders_morning_line_odds) · Betting Info · International Horse Racing   
[Horse Racing News](http://www.horseracegame.com/community) · Famous Race Horses · Game Reviews   
Privacy Policy
